Guide to the Sean F. Killeen Lead Belly research collection, 1885-2002
Lead Belly research collection
- Series III. Correspondence
  - Subseries IIIa. Individuals: correspondence and research
    - Gilbert, F.S., 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Gilston, Mark, 1990-1993 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1991-1997 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Gleason, Ralph, 1939-1977; 1994 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Gormanous, Greg, 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Gossa, Tsegaye: Gossa Vision (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Gottlieb, William, 1939-1943; 1991-1996 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Gracyk, Tim, 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Green, Archie, 1965-1971; 1991-1998 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Greenhill, Manny, 1992-1996 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Greer, Lucia "Chia", 1948-1995 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Greiss, Abe, 1956-1962; 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Gross, Terry: WHYY-FM, 1991-1996 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Grossman, Stefan, 1950; 1992-1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Grossman, Sid, 1918; 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Gruhn Guitars, 1988-1995 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Guralnick, Peter, 1976-1995 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Guthrie, Woody (1), 1940-1980; 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Guthrie, Woody (2), 1940-1980; 1990-2000 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Haley, Alex (1), 1961-1983; 1991-1999 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Haley, Alex (2), 1961-1983; 1991-1999 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Hammond, John, 1939-1988; 1995-1999 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Hatley, Donald, 1949-1989; 1991-2000 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Hayes, Walter, 1394-1967; 1994-1997 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Hebald, Milton: Troubador Sculpture, 1937-1986; 1998 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Hellerman, Fred, 1951-1953; 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Henley, Don, 1894-1996 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Hentoff, Nat, 1940-1959; 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Hickenson, Joe, 1937-1988; 1990-1998 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Hinton, Sam, 1944-1958; 1993-1998 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Hirsch, Jerrold, 1943; 1988; 1992-1996 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Hodes, Art, 1939-1974; 1992-1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Holiday, Billie, 1943-1950; 1995-2000 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Horne, Lena, 1943; 1965 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Hughes, Langston, 1948-1960; 1991-1996 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Hughes, Sheriff Thomas, 1917-1987; 1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Hurston, Zora Neale: archival materials (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Hurston, Zora Neale: biographical and critical articles, 1936-1991 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Hurston, Zora Neale: biographical and critical articles, 1992-2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Hurston, Zora Neale: notes and correspondence (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Hurston, Zora Neale: writings and reviews (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Irish, Keith: correspondence, 1991-1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Ives, Burl, 1945-1995 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Jackson, Bruce, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Jackson, Harry, 1969-2000 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - James, Dante, 1994-2000 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Jefferson, Blind Lemon, 1926-2000 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Johnson, David, 1947-1996 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Johnson, Hewlett, 1941-1998 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Johnson, Jack, 1991-1998 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Johnson, Lisa, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - JOMO, a.k.a. Tom Kobela, 1993-1998 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Jones, Elaine R., 1993-1999 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Jones, James Earl, 1969-1992 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Joplin, Janis, 1969-1999 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Jones, Max and McCarthy, Albert J., 1993-1997 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Jones, Sissieretta ("Black Patti"), 1947-2000 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Jordon, Clifford, 1965-1999 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Kandell, Leslie (Barbara Biber and LIttle Red Schol House history), 1922-1984 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Handell, Leslie (Correspondence and articles), 1924-2000 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Kantno, Josh, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Kesey, Ken, 1959-1999 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Kinzer, Stephen, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Klose, Michael, 1990-1997 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Knight, Ralph, 1964-1996 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Kottke, Leo, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Kuralt, Charles, 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1959-1994 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Landry, Virginia, 1938-1997 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Langley, Graham, 1946-1998 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - LaVere, Stephen, 1944-2000 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Lawson, Jennifer and PBS, 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Ledbetter, Martha Promise, 1925-1990 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Lee, Hector, 1946-1963; 1991-1993 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Lee, Peggy, 1944-2002 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Lester, Julius, 1938-1998 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Leventhal, Harold, 1990-2002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Lewman, Harry, 1993-1997 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Lieberman, Robbie, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Loach, Graham, 1995-1998 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Lomax, Alan (1), 1938-2000 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Lomax, Alan (2), 1938-2000 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Lomax, Bess, 1940-1995 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Lomax, John (1), 1917-1997 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Lomax, John (2), 1917-1997 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Lomax, John III, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Larthridge, Jim, 1991-1995 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Lornell, Kip, 1991-1998 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - McDonald, Joe, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - McFatter, Dwayne, 1991-1995 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - McGhee, Brownie, 1950-1996 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - McCormack, Mack, 1960-1992 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Martin, David Stone, 1991-1998 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Martin, Francis (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Martin, Phil, 1984-1989 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Melendez, Ramon, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Merson, Marc, 1976-1996 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - McInerny, Dennis, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Midgley, Trevor, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Mitford, Jessica, 1950-1996 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Morgan, Michael J., 1990-1998 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Morris, Malcolm, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Mosley, Robin, 1972-1993 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Moyers, Bill, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Muhlstock, Louis, 1980-1997 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Muldaur, Maria, 1991-2001 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Morrison, Van, 1975-2000 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Neff, Pat (1), 1921-1994 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Nef, Pat (2), 1921-1994 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Neff, Pat (3), 1921-1994 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Newton, Francis (a.k.a. Eric Hobsbawm), 1960-1994 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Ney, Lew (a.k.a. Luther E. Widen), 1942-1948 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Nickson, Richard, 1944-1997 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Nigro, Deborah M., 1991-1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Norman, Kenneth, 1996-1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Nowlin, Bill, 1992-2000 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Oakley, Giles, 1917-1997 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Obrecht, Jas (article drafts), 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Obrecht, Jas (articles and magazines), 1935-1997 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Obrecht, Jas (correspondence, articles, and notes), 1939-1996 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Odetta, 1958-2000 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Oliver, Paul, 1959-1997 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Owens, Rochelle, 1971-? (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Parks, Gordon, 1942-2000 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Patton, Mark, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Paul, Irving, 1935-1992 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Peck, Gregory, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Petric, Faith, 1962-1998 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Pierce, Robert, 1987-1997 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Porterfield, Nolan, 1933-1999 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Poston, Ted, 1940-1974 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Price, John Andrew, 1977-1996 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Rainey, Ma, 1940-1992 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Priums, Pearl, 1943-1994 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Randle, Bill, 1946-1996 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Ramsey, Frederic, Jr., 1939-1995 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Ray, Nicholas, 1940-1994 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Reynolds, John, 1941-2000 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Reynolds, John: newspapers, photos and cards, 1919-2000 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Ritchie, Jean, 1989-2000 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Rideau, Wilbert, 1949-1999 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Ringqvist, Claes, 1941-1996 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Ritter, Tex, 1935-1998 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Robeson, Paul, 1928-2001 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Robinson, Early, 1930-1999 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Robinson, Queen "Tiny", 1944-1999 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Rosen, Kenneth, 1991-1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Russell, Ross, 1941-1998 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Rustin, Bayard, 1948-1997 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Sandburg, Carl, 1968-1991 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Sanders, Betty, 1924-1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Santelli, Robert: Rock and Roll Hall of Fame, 1984-1998 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Scarborough, Dorothy, 1919-1990 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Schroeder, Rebecca "Becky", 1989-1999 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Schwarzer, Helmut, 1968-1994 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Seeger, Anthony "Tony", 1946-1957; 1987-2000 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Seeger, Mike, 1964; 1992-1995 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Seeger, Pete: Incomplete Folksongs (1), 1935-1971; 1988-2000 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Seeger, Pete: Incomplete Folksongs (2), 1935-1971; 1988-2000 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Singorelli, Catherine, 1941-1974; 1992-1996 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Silverman, Gerlad "Jerry": NYU 1950 MS Thesis, Blues Guitar, 1955-1958; 1982-1995 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Singer, Sean, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Smith, Bessie, 1915-1995 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Smith, Richard D., 1950-1979; 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Sobin, Dennis, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Spivey, Victoria, 1963-1976 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Spottswood, Dick, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Stevens, Marshall, 1940-1964; 1990 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Steck, Bob, 1936-1767; 1993-1996 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Stern,. Tom, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Sutter, John: NY Folklore Society, 1935-1985; 1992-1996 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - "Taj Mahal", 1990-2000 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Taylor, Bruce, 1988-1996 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Taylor, T.J.: Probate Records, 1919-1926 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Thomas, Steve, 1989-1997 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Thompson, Harold W., 1934-1964; 1991-1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Todd, Charles "Cafe" L., 1946-1984; 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Toland, Rey, 1966; 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Tolbert, Frank, 1970-1983; 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Trachtenberg, Alan, 1991-1994 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Trudeau, Robert, 1990-1997 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Van Matre, Lynn: Chicago Tribune, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Verschaeren, Dirk, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Von Schmidt, Eric, 1947-1987; 1991-1995 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Walsh, Paul, 1949-1997 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Walters, Matt: Roots Records, 1994-1997 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Warner, Jeff and Frank, 1944-1984; 1991-1999 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Weber, Jane, 1997-2000 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Weissman, Dick: Paper '56, 1956; 1995 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Welles, Orson, 1978-1996 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Charles White, 1943-1945; 1960-1986; 1997-2001 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Josh White, 1940-1963; 1991-2001 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Williams, Clarence (1), 1915-1980; 1992-2002 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Williams, Clarence (2), 1915-1980; 1992-2002 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Williams, Clarence (3), 1915-1980; 1992-2002 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Williams, Chester, 1923-1974; 1993-1997 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Williams, Mary Lou, 1944-1983; 1994-2001 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Wilson,. George, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Winan, Fonville, 1946-1989; 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Witten, Patti, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Wolfe, Charles, 1992-1999 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Wright, Richard, 1937-1973; 1991-1995 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Wyatt, Lorre, 1993-1996 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Young, Izzy, 1935-1968; 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Young, Neil, 1992-2000 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Yurcheno, Henrietta, 1940-1987; 1991-2000 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Subseries IIIb. Fan Mail
    - Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1940, 1960s (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 6-7)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 8-9)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 10-12)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 13-14)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Subseries IIIc. Miscellaneous Correspondence
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence 2 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence 3 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence 4 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Rounder records CD graphics (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence and envelopes (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Letter photocopies (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Series IV. Publications, Penitentiary Research, and Discography
  - Lomax: Negro Folk Songs as Sung by Lead Belly, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Morgan: "Just a Real Song": Huddie Leadbetter (Lead Belly) and African American Oral Traditions (dissertation), 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Asch and Lomax: The Leadbelly Songbook, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - TRO Folkways: Leadbelly; Campbell: Leadbelly, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Chambers: Leadbelly -- Balling the Blues (play), 1990-1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Lester and Seeger: The Folksinger's Guide to: the 12-String Guitar as Played by Leadbelly, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Garvin and Addeo: The Midnight Special: the Legend of Lead Belly, 1971-1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Lomax and Wood: Leadbelly: a Collection of World-Famous Songs by Huddie Ledbetter, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Lomax and Wood: The Leadbelly Legend, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Shreveport, LA, 1895-1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Shreveport, LA (2), 1895-1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Shreveport, LA (3), 1895-1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Shreveport, LA: books, 1896-1985 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Shreveport, LA: books (cont.), 1896-1985 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Books (music), 1947-1998 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Books: folk/blues/jazz music, 1903-1995 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Books: folk/blues/jazz music (2), 1903-1995 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Books: folk/blues/jazz music (3), 1903-1995 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Articles (foreign), 1957-1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Articles: A-C (by author), 1919-1995 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Articles: D-E, 1916-1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Articles: F-H, 1895-1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Articles: I-J, 1927-1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Articles: K, 1869-1995 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Articles: L, 1935-1994 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Articles: M-N, 1925-1993 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Articles: O-R, 1934-1994 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Articles: S-U, 1912-1993 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Articles: V-Z, 1918-1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Journal articles, citations, 1954-1995 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Discography, 1940-1995 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Discography (2), 1940-1995 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Discography (3), 1940-1995 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Angola, 1991-1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Angola (2), 1930-1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Angold (3), 1882-1997 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Angola (4), 1930-1996 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Angola (5), 1928-1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Angola (6), 1929-1999 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Jackson, LA, 1927-1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Rikers Island, 1930-2001 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Rikers Island (cont.), 1930-2001 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Texas Penitentiary System, 1924-1999 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Texas Penitentiary System (cont.), 1924-1999 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Huntsville, TX, 1897-1990 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Huntsville, TX (cont.), 1897-1990 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Record album sleeves and liner notes, 1935-1995 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Record album sleeves and liner notes (2), 1947-1995 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Record album sleeves and liner notes (3), 1976-1996 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Series V. Audio and Visual Materials
  - Subseries Va. CDs, Disks, and Tape Recordings
    - “Leadbelly, Important Recordings 1934-1949” collection (master copies), CD-1676-1679 (Box 22)
    - Leadbelly last sessions, TR-9504-9507 (Box 26)
    - Elektra, Leadbelly, TR-9508-9510 (Box 26)
    - Leadbelly: Library of Congress, TR-9511-9512 (Box 26)
    - Stinson, TR-9513-9514 (Box 26)
    - FA Leadbelly, TR-9515-9517 (Box 26)
    - Jack of Diamonds, 1934; TR-9518 (Box 26)
    - Radio programs, 1990-1992; TR-9519-9539 (Box 26)
    - Barnicle-Cadle Collection, TR-9540-9546 (Box 26)
    - Recordings and covers by other artists, TR-9547-9599 (Box 26)
    - Early Leadbelly recordings, 1938-1949; TR-9600-9608 (Box 26)
    - Leadbelly tapes, TR-9609-9615 (Box 26)
    - Interview tapes, TR-9616-9673 (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous recordings, TR-9674-9680 (Box 26)
    - Reel-to-reel tapes, TR-9681-9683 (Box 28)
    - Floppy Disks, information (Box 28)
  - Subseries Vb. DVDs, VHS, Microfilm
    - "The Definitive Leadbelly" collection (master copies), CD-1673-1675 (Box 22)
      -Includes DVD-806
    - “Leadbelly” (master copy), DVD-807 (Box 22)
    - Leadbelly and Irene, V-6627-6629 (Box 27)
    - Ithaca Trolleys, 1988; V-6630-6631 (Box 27)
    - Johnson Museum of Art, 1997; V-6632-6634 (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous performances, dedications and interviews, V-6635-6660 (Box 27)
    - Video performances by other artists, V-6661-6665 (Box 27)
    - Television programs, V-6666-6682 (Box 28)
    - Seminar of 7, V-6683-6685 (Box 28)
    - Legacy of Leadbelly, V-6686-6691 (Box 28)
    - Unlabelled, V-6692-6693 (Box 28)
    - Microfilm reel, Barbara Ledbetter (Box 28)
  - Subseries Vc. Photographs
    - Leadbelly with children performances, photocopies and originals (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Max Jones articles with photographs (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Illness, obituary, memorial photographs and clippings (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - "Goes to Pioneer" (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Life Magazine photographs with article, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Photocopies (Box 24, Folder 23-24)
    - Miscellaneous photographs (Box 24, Folder 25)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
The Rise and Fall of Jim Crow, 2003, by Richard Wormser
leadbelly, 2005, by Tyehimba Jess
Lead Belly, a life in pictures, 2008, edited by Tiny Robinson and John Reynalds with introduction by Tom Waits/Poems by Jess and foreword by Glenn O’Brien
Texas Tough, the rise of America’s prison empire, 2010, by Robert Perkinson